Everything interesting begins in the mind
Basic Instinct 2 is a crime, mystery, thriller film
directed by Michael Caton-Jones.
Novelist Catherine Tramell is once again in trouble with the
law, and Scotland Yard appoints psychiatrist Dr.
Michael Glass to evaluate her.
Though, like Detective Nick Curran before him, Glass is
entranced by Tramell and lured into a seductive game.
Catherine Tramell, played by Sharon Stone.
Michael Glass, played by David Morrissey.
Milena Gardosh, played by Charlotte Rampling.
Roy Washburn, played by David Thewlis.
Kevin Franks, played by Stan Collymore.
Denise Glass, played by Indira Varma.
Basic Instinct 2 (also known as Basic Instinct 2: Risk Addiction) is a 2006 erotic
thriller film directed by Michael Caton-Jones, produced by Mario Kassar, Joel B.
Michaels, and Andrew G.
Vajna, and written by Leora Barish and Henry Bean.
The sequel to Basic Instinct (1992), it stars Sharon Stone, who reprises her
role of the crime novelist Catherine Tramell, and David Morrissey.
The film was an international co-production of German,
British, American, and Spanish production companies.
The film follows novelist and suspected serial killer Catherine Tramell, who is
once again in trouble with the authorities, this time in London.
Now Scotland Yard (Greater London's Metropolitan
Police Service) appoints psychiatrist Dr.
Michael Glass to evaluate her.
As with SFPD Detective Nick Curran in the first film, Dr.
Glass becomes a victim of Tramell's psychological manipulation.
After being in development limbo for several years, the sequel film was shot in
London from April to August 2005, and was released on 31 March 2006.
It received negative reviews and underperformed at the box office.
The film explores themes of soho london, jacuzzi, erotic thriller.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.